[ rustling ]
♪ ♪
[ chirping ]
Today we are going to pretend to be trees .
We 're gonna be tall , wonderful , green trees
with really long branches and lush leaves .
So , if you 'll stand up for me .
[ imitating wind blowing ]
What 's that noise ? Can anybody hear it ?
- Wind . - [ gasps ] Wind .
[ all imitate wind blowing ]
And then suddenly ...
- there 's a storm . - [ kids laughing ]
[ imitates wind howling ]
[ indistinct chatter ]
- Bye bye . - Bye .
- Hey . - Hi .
How 's the house hunting going ?
Yeah , uh , it 's okay , I mean , it 's just been going on and on .
Well , take my advice , pounce now . Market 's going through the roof .
Yeah , we 're gonna drop and see estate agents later , so ...
Well , don 't get left behind , Gemma .
[ chuckles ] Okay , bye .
Who did that to the poor baby birds ?
I don 't know .
Maybe it was a cuckoo .
Why ?
Because it needed a nest .
Why doesn 't it just make its own nest ?
Because that 's nature , that 's just the way things are .
I don 't like the way things are . They 're terrible .
Well ...
- It 's only horrible sometimes . - [ woman ] Molly .
- Bye , Ms. Pierce . - Bye .
[ Tom imitates wind blowing ]
[ Tom ] Hey there , little lady . Come a little closer .
- [ chuckles ] - Nah-ah !
Come on , Mr. Tree wants to get to know you .
Ah , there you go . There you go .
[ groans ]
[ groans ] My bark .
- [ Gemma chuckles ] - [ Tom grunts ]
- Hey . - Hi .
Mm . So , how am I at the tree game ?
- Yeah , you 're pretty mediocre . - That 's good .
[ sighs ] Sad little things .
It 's cruel .
[ sighs ]
Okay , there you go .
[ imitates wind blowing ]
[ sighs ]
- [ chanting ] - [ Gemma chuckles ]
Hey , come on . Show some respect .
- Did you knock them down ? - No , I did not knock them down .
I am a professional . Come on . How dare you ?
- Professional weirdo . - Yeah , but professional .
Professional . [ continues chanting ]
[ Tom ] I 'm gonna get my own wheels one day .
Just you wait , I 'm gonna have , like , a big , you know ,
muddy gardener 's van .
- [ Gemma ] Sounds delightful . - Yeah .
Are you gonna change your T-shirt ?
- What ? - Your T-shirt .
- Seriously ? - Yeah .
- Shit . - You stink .
- [ shop bell rings ] - [ indistinct chatter ]
[ Tom ] Yo , seriously . Your mom , she 's the worst offender , too .
[ Gemma ] She 's hardly over there .
[ Tom ] She 's there all the time .
[ Gemma ] Well , she came with the apartment .
- [ Tom chuckles ] Yeah . - [ footsteps approaching ]
Hello .
We 're just , um ...
- looking ... - Yeah .
- ... for something ... - And you are ?
I 'm Gemma . This is my boyfriend , Tom .
Hey , what 's up ?
Gemma and Tom , lovely to meet you .
It 's lovely to meet you too , Martin .
Yonder is a wonderful development .
Both tranquil and practical , it has all you 'd need and all you 'd want .
And as for the prices ,
it 's no wonder these houses are getting snapped up . [ laughs ]
[ Tom snickers ]
I know what you guys are thinking .
Suburbia .
But there 's more to Yonder than what you see in these images .
We 've lovely people , all sorts of people ready to move in .
It 's going to be a diverse community .
Something different , a nice blend .
Where 's it located ?
Near enough .
And far enough .
Just the right distance .
[ gasps ] We could take a look , if you like .
- [ Tom ] Hmm . - Do you have a vehicle ?
- Ah , shit . Unfortunately ... - Yes , we do , outside .
Good . I 'll get my keys . You can follow me .
[ sighs ]
We could arrange an appointment at a later date , if you 'd prefer .
But like I said , homes at Yonder may not be available for much longer .
[ Tom ] All right .
It 's not exactly what we 're looking for , but , um ...
- I suppose it 's ... - Worth a look ?
Good . We 're all happy , then .
[ chuckles ]
[ snickers ] Jesus .
Martin , you are one strange and persuasive motherfucker .
- Oh . - Ready .
- [ Tom ] Yeah , ready , yeah . - [ Gemma ] Ready .
[ " Rudy , A Message to You " by Dandy Livingstone playing ]
♪ Stop your runnin ' about ♪
♪ It 's time you straighten right out ♪
♪ Stop your runnin ' around ♪
♪ Making trouble in the town ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Rudy ♪
♪ A message to you , Rudy ♪
♪ A message to you ♪
[ humming ]
Okay . Here we go .
♪ A message to you , Rudy ♪
♪ A message to you ♪
♪ You 're growing older each day ♪
♪ You want to think of your future ♪
♪ Or you might wind up in jail ... ♪
- [ car beeps ] - Okay .
- Let 's get this over with . - [ car door opens ]
Okay .
- Welcome to Yonder . - [ Tom ] Thank you .
Number nine .
[ door closes ]
Many homes have the pretense of being ideal .
But these homes really are ideal .
Please go through .
Toasty .
- It 's ... - Yeah .
Oh .
The living room . A room to live in .
Memories will be made in the ample spaces between these walls . [ chuckles ]
- Come . - [ Tom snickers ]
- It 's good , it 's good . - [ Gemma chuckles ]
I love it . I love the single hue .
- A welcome tipple . - [ chuckles ]
- I 'm ... I 'm driving . - Mm .
- Perhaps a strawberry . - Oh , no . I 'm ... I 'm driving .
Blue for a boy .
You 've got it all worked out .
Number nine is not a starter home .
- This house is forever . - [ Tom ] Hmm .
A perfect environment for a young family .
Do you have children ?
No . Not yet .
[ imitates Gemma ] No . Not yet .
- The master bedroom . - [ Tom ] Yeah .
If you follow me to the back garden .
A haven of nature .
It 's good , it 's nice here .
- Yeah . - If you wanna ...
live here , it 's a lot of space .
So , when 're people due to move in ?
[ Tom ] Huh ?
[ Gemma ] Martin ?
Martin ?
- Hello ? - Nope .
- His car 's gone . - Huh ?
His car 's gone .
Good . Now , let 's get the fuck out of here .
[ car door opens ]
[ car door closes ]
- Okie dokes . - [ car engine starts ]
♪ ♪
Buh-bye .
- That guy was so strange . - Yeah .
Wait . No , no , I don 't think this is the right way .
- Yeah , this is the way we came in . - No , is it ?
[ Gemma ] Yeah .
Wait .
- What ? You think it was back there ? - Yeah , I think it was back there .
Let me just see what 's around here , though .
Number nine again . Did we just do some kind of loop ?
[ Gemma ] What the fuck ?
Wait , did we ... Did we leave the door open ?
How 've we just ...
♪ ♪
You want me to drive ?
- No , I 'm good . - Yeah ? You 're good ?
' Cause I think we 're literally going in a circle .
Tom .
All right .
- Give me the wheel . - What ?
What difference is that gonna make ?
Okay . Come on . Give me a go .
- You wanna go ? - Yeah .
- You wanna go on the car ? - Yeah .
- What are you ? Six ? - Yeah , I 'm six .
- Come on , just move over . - [ sighs ]
Fine . [ grunts ]
[ grunting ] I 'll give you a go .
A little go of the car .
- [ seatbelts fastens ] - Okay . Let 's go .
- Do you have your phone ? - Yeah .
[ Tom ] Anything ?
No , there 's no coverage on either of them .
Great .
- Tom . - What ?
[ Gemma ] Number fucking nine again .
- Hmm . - Fuck this .
Ooh , you 're not doing that in my car .
- I 'm opening the window . - [ window opens ]
You 're such a jerk .
- One second , I 'm stressed . - [ scoffs ]
[ Tom inhales ]
- [ window closes ] - Okay , let 's go . Thank you .
[ chuckles ]
[ Tom ] Number nine .
Why the fuck do we keep seeing number nine ?
I haven 't seen a single car . There 's nobody here .
[ Gemma ] If I see another row of green houses ...
[ Tom ] Okay , who the fuck would live in this place ?
- ... I 'm gonna lose my mind . - [ Tom ] This shit is not possible , okay ?
- It 's not possible . - [ Gemma ] We got in here ...
[ overlapping speech ]
[ Gemma ] Tom , we have gone this way .
- I have gone this way that 's ... - [ Tom ] All right , no , no , just ...
- Just let me figure this out ... - ... where you took the wheel .
[ overlapping speech ]
[ Gemma ] Please , can you just listen to me once ? I think we should take a left .
- [ Tom ] I know what I 'm doing . - [ Gemma ] You 've done this , like ,
- five or six times now . - I know what I 'm doing .
- I know what I 'm doing . - [ overlapping speech echoes ]
[ Gemma ] It just goes on and on and on .
[ car engine stops ]
[ car engine sputtering ]
- [ sputtering continues ] - [ fuel indicator dings ]
It 's empty .
- Oh , my God . - [ sighs ]
[ echoing ] Hello ?
[ Gemma 's voice echoes ]
Hello !
[ footsteps approaching ]
Let 's go inside .
No taste .
[ whispering ] I 've never heard such silence .
Well ...
Come here .
All right . Hold the base with your foot .
Be careful .
Okay . [ exhales ]
[ grunts ]
♪ ♪
Well , what do you see ?
Tom , what do you see ?
Hey , maybe ... Maybe we should follow the sun .
We 'll ... We 'll cut through gardens , we 'll jump over fences ,
what ... Whatever it takes , all right ? We 're ... We 're gonna get out of here .
[ Tom breathes heavily ]
♪ ♪
- [ Tom pants ] - Are you okay ?
[ panting continues ]
Yeah .
- [ both pant ] - [ Gemma grunts ]
[ Tom ] I ... I 've gotta stop . I 've gotta stop .
[ pants ]
- Tom , there 's a light . - [ panting ] A light ?
There 's a light .
[ both pant ]
- Holy shit . - Hello ?
Hello .
[ door opens ]
- [ Gemma ] Hello ? - [ both panting ]
[ Tom ] What 's happening ?
[ Tom breathing hard ]
What the fuck ?
Come back !
Hey ! Hey ! Come back !
- What have you done ? - I 'm sending out a smoke signal .
[ debris rumbling ]
[ fire cracking ]
[ baby coos ]
[ cooing continues ]
[ Tom groans ]
Oh , my God .
[ gasps ]
Hi .
It 's a boy .
[ door creaks ]
[ Gemma groans ]
[ Tom groans ]
[ Tom sighs ]
[ imitates Gemma ] Someone must be watching .
[ imitates Tom ] There must be some way out of here ,
everywhere has a way out .
[ imitates Gemma 's cry ]
[ boy imitating Tom ] Yeah , well , maybe , Gemma , if you didn 't say no
to every other goddamn house we looked at , we wouldn 't have ended up here .
[ imitates Gemma ] So , I 'm to blame ? How is this my fault , Tom ?
I 'm sorry , Gem , it 's just this place is making me crazy .
[ imitates Gemma ] The food here makes me feel sick .
Creepy little mutant .
Measure me . Measure me , measure me .
Am I bigger today ?
Yes . You 're bigger today .
- I grow fast as a dog . - That 's right .
What is a dog ?
We already told you what a dog is .
- Woof , woof , woof ! - Yes . Woof , woof , woof , woof .
[ boy imitates barking ]
Are you overwhelmed again , Mother ?
I am not your mother .
Who is my mother ?
God knows .
Dog knows . Dog knows . [ continues barking ]
[ screams ]
Yum yum .
[ Tom sighs ]
[ Gemma ] I don 't know why we do this .
They never seem to come when we 're waiting to bash their brains out with a pick .
- It 's futile . - Yeah .
Like putting an SOS on the roof when planes never seem to pass , right ?
Yep .
Watching .
That boy is always watching .
That 's not a boy .
Coffee ?
Yeah , sure .
[ sizzles ]
[ Tom grunts ]
♪ ♪
[ Gemma grunts ]
[ Tom grunts ]
This is just pointless , it 's just weird muck .
[ grunts ]
The box is gone .
[ Tom continues grunting ]
Did you ... Did you move the box ?
- Tell me . - Where 're the roots ?
- Tom . - Where 's the subsoil ?
- Where 's anything ? - It 's gone . I was right here .
I was standing right here . I was looking at the road .
Tom . Tom !
- Stop ! - Gemma , please ! Just let me dig , okay ?
This is something I can do . Please just let me do this .
[ Tom grunts ]
[ Tom breathing heavily ]
[ Tom sighs ]
- You were digging all day . - [ panting ]
- All day , Tom . - Yeah .
Why ?
It 's got to have a bottom .
It 's gotta ... It 's gotta lead to somewhere .
- Where ? - I don 't know .
- Australia . - [ scoffs ]
Yeah , baby .
- Or hell . - No .
No , we 're already there .
[ door opens ]
[ shower running ]
[ both panting ]
[ kissing ]
All right , I 'm gonna head back out .
Oh , well , wait for me , I 'll come with you .
No , you know what ? We only got the ... the one spade .
Well , I could use the pick .
You know , it kinda comes off in clumps now . But , thanks .
[ door opens ]
[ door closes ]
[ exhales , groans ]
[ scraping ]
[ coughing ]
- [ boy imitates barking ] - [ washing machine whirring ]
[ crackles ]
[ Tom pants ]
[ Tom sighs ]
There 's like a smell in this car .
It 's not bad , it 's just like ... It 's like a real smell .
- Have you noticed that ? Yeah . - Yeah .
I like it . I 've just been ...
breathing it in ...
pretending that I 'm home .
[ " 007 Shanty Town " by Desmond Dekker playing ]
The battery 's still good , Jesus .
♪ 007 ♪
♪ At ocean eleven ♪
♪ And the rude boys go a wail ♪
♪ ' Cause them out ofjail ♪
♪ Rude boys cannot fail ♪
[ volume increases ] ♪ ' Cause they must get bail ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Dem a loot , dem a shoot , dem a wail ♪
♪ A shanty town ♪
♪ Dem rude boys get a probation ♪
♪ And rude boy a bomb up the town ♪
♪ A shanty town ♪
♪ 007 ♪
♪ At ocean eleven ♪
♪ And the rude boys a go wail ♪
♪ ' Cause them out ofjail ♪
♪ Rude boys cannot fail ♪
- ♪ ' Cause them must get bail ♪ - [ groans ]
- [ radio turns off ] - [ laughs ] Tom .
Tom , you okay ?
- [ grunts ] - Tom !
Are you all right ?
Let me see .
[ door slams ]
Are you okay ?
We can 't be with you all the time .
People like to be alone sometimes , okay ?
Do you understand ?
Not being with each other all the time .
Forget it .
- Goodnight . - Goodnight , Mother .
I 'm not your mother .
[ door closes ]
[ screams ]
What the fuck ?
What do you want ? We fed you .
- What do you want ? - [ screaming continues ]
Jesus ! Say what you want . What do you want ?
Shut up . Shut up !
Shut up ! Shut up !
- Shut up ! - [ boy stops screaming ]
[ imitates Tom ] Gemma , please , just let me do this , okay ?
This is something I can do . Just please , Gemma , let me do this .
You 're fucking disgusting .
- [ as Tom ] Please , Gemma , just please . - Do you know that ?
[ as Tom ] Just please let me do this .
- This is something I can do ... - You 're fucking disgusting !
Please , Gemma , let me do ...
[ door closes ]
- [ urinating ] - [ footsteps approaching ]
[ Tom coughs ]
[ flushes ]
[ Tom ] Sorry .
[ Gemma ] It 's okay .
[ screams ]
[ imitating Gemma ] I am fucking disgusting , you know that ?
I am fucking disgusting .
Are you gonna dig today ?
Yeah . Yeah , I guess .
Do you feel like you 're making progress ?
Yeah .
Yeah . So , I 'm gonna , um ... I 'm gonna get back to it .
Thanks .
[ door closes ]
[ grunting ]
[ creature shrieking in distance ]
[ creature continues shrieking ]
[ grunting ]
- [ as Gemma ] What the fuck ! - [ Gemma ] Go to bed .
- [ as Gemma ] Go to bed . - Listen to me . Go to bed .
[ as Gemma ] Listen to me , go to bed .
- Stop ! - [ as Gemma ] Stop .
[ creature shrieking ]
[ gasps ]
[ static ]
Gemma .
No .
On .
- No . - On !
No !
What am I supposed to do with him ?
[ static ]
Whatever .
[ as Gemma ] Whatever .
[ boy screaming ]
[ screaming stops ]
- What are you doing ? - [ boy screaming ]
- [ boy stops screaming ] - Tom !
- [ boy screaming ] - I 'm locking it up .
I 'm gonna starve it .
- Tom . Tom . - Gemma , stay !
[ boy continues screaming ]
All right . Get in . Come on .
- [ screaming continues ] - Give me the key .
- No , no . Get back in the house . - Give me the key !
- Get back in the house ! - Tom . Tom !
- Gemma , come on . - Tom , give me the key !
[ screaming ]
- [ both grunt ] - I am not looking after it , okay ?
You will leave it there . Don 't play with it , don 't feed it ,
don 't have anything to do with it . You will let it starve .
- Let me up ! - Look , it has you acting
like you 're its fucking mother , okay ?
You 're putting it to bed at night , you 're telling it not to watch cartoons .
- Tom , let me up ! - [ both panting ]
♪ ♪
[ both panting ]
Look , I 'm sorry , but I ... I will not let you help it .
Okay ? If they don 't want it to die , they 'll come for it .
It 's up to them .
[ screaming ]
What if they don 't come ?
What are we supposed to do ? Do we just sit here and we wait for him to die ?
- It . - What ?
It . Not him .
Stop saying him .
If it dies , maybe they 'll let us go .
- [ keys jingling ] - Hey .
Hey , it 's okay .
He 's not gonna hurt you , I promise .
You can come out .
I 'm sorry .
♪ ♪
- [ grunting ] - [ digging ]
[ pants ]
Do you hear me ?
I can hear you .
[ Tom coughs ]
He 'll get tired soon .
And he 'll go to sleep .
You should go to sleep , too .
Have a dream .
What 's a dream ?
It 's , um ...
It 's like all sorts of moving pictures in your mind ,
but no one else can see them .
I 've never had a dream .
Well ...
close your eyes and try .
♪ ♪
[ Tom ] Whoever 's on the other side , can you hear me ?
I know you can hear me .
[ Tom shouting indistinctly ]
Can you hear me ? I know you 're out there .
[ sighs ]
[ groans ]
[ grunts ]
[ sighs ]
[ coughs ]
[ door opens ]
♪ ♪
[ boy ] What lovely sky we have .
It is lovely to live under a lovely sky
and a lovely house with lovely houses all around us .
You are such a mystery .
You 're a mystery and I 'm gonna solve you .
I 'm a mystery . I 'm a mystery .
Do you see that cloud ? What 's that cloud in the shape of ?
[ boy ] A cloud .
That 's right .
Do you see that other cloud ?
- Yes . - What 's that cloud in the shape of ?
- A cloud . - Yes .
Another cloud-shaped cloud .
All the clouds here are shaped like clouds .
Perfect , sickening ...
little clouds .
Do you like clouds ?
Where I come from ...
clouds come in all shapes and sizes ,
some of them look like faces
and some of them look like dogs .
Woof , woof !
[ both barking ]
[ howling ]
[ cries ]
[ sniffs ]
[ crying continues ]
♪ ♪
- [ digging ] - [ Tom grunting ]
[ grunts ]
[ Tom grunting ]
Did you see the boy ?
No . [ grunts ]
- He 's gone missing . - Well ...
so have we .
- [ Gemma ] Hello ! - [ voice echoes ]
- Where are you ? - [ voice echoes ]
Where did you go ?
- [ digging ] - [ Tom grunts ]
♪ ♪
[ coughs ]
[ static ]
Where were you today ?
I was solving a mystery .
Really ?
- What did you discover ? - Lots .
- Lots ? Like what ? - Lots and lots .
Did you meet anyone when you were solving the mystery ?
I met you when I was finished .
Did you meet anyone else ?
Anyone you 've never met before ?
Who ?
I 'm not allowed to say .
[ button clicks ]
Let 's play a game .
Let 's play pretend .
Pretend to be me .
[ as Gemma , sighs ] Whatever .
Can you pretend to be Tom ?
[ as Tom ] Gemma , stay !
- Will I do a dog ? - Yes , please .
[ barking ]
Is there anyone else you can do ?
Someone you met today ?
Pretend to be that person .
[ takes deep breath ]
[ groans ]
[ shrieking ]
[ gasps , sobs ]
Are you overwhelmed again , Mother ?
I am not your mother !
Are you overwhelmed ?
I want ... to go home .
[ chuckles ]
Silly Mother , you are home .
♪ ♪
[ utensils clattering ]
- Thanks . - You 're welcome .
Do you mean that ?
Or is that sarcasm ? Are you being sarcastic ?
No .
But you don 't really mean that I 'm welcome , right ?
I was being polite .
Why are you being polite ?
Is it fear ?
Probably .
[ as Gemma ] Probably .
[ wheezing ]
[ coughing ]
[ grunts ]
[ Tom sighs ]
You need to eat something .
I 'll try . [ grunts ]
Thank you .
What 's wrong ?
Why didn 't I let you kill him when he was young ?
Because you 're a ... you 're a good person .
♪ ♪
[ Tom coughing ]
Thanks .
You like playing this game , don 't you ?
[ panting ]
[ grunting ]
[ coughs ]
[ grunts ]
[ breathing heavily ]
[ metal clanks ]
[ gasps ]
[ breathes heavily ]
♪ ♪
- Tom ! - [ voice echoes ]
- Gemma . - [ voice echoes ]
Tom !
- Gemma ! - [ voice echoes ]
- Gemma ! - [ Tom 's voice echoes ]
[ panting ]
Gemma !
- Tom ? - [ voice echoes ]
[ breathes heavily , grunts ]
[ breathing heavily ] Gem ...
Gem ...
[ exhales ]
Tom .
[ pants ] Hi .
It 's locked .
Hey , open the door !
- Let us in . - [ banging on window ]
Open ! Open the door !
Open the door !
[ Tom grunts ]
Tom .
- Tom . - [ grunts ]
Shit .
Please .
Please , please , please . You need to help us ,
' cause he 's getting sicker and sicker .
Please , you can 't leave him this way .
You know , maybe it 's time he was released .
♪ ♪
[ lighter clicks ]
[ exhales ]
Do you remember ...
the wind ...
Gemma ?
Before we got here .
- Yeah . - The wind was great .
I never realized how much I liked it .
I 'm glad that guy stood you up .
You looked so glum .
I didn 't know if it was okay for me to go over and , like , talk to you .
You looked so glum , so cute .
I can 't even remember what I said .
You didn 't say anything , you just ... stood next to me .
Oh , shit .
That 's creepy .
You told me I looked like I needed a drink .
- You did . - Mm-hmm .
- You said I looked like I needed one too . - Mm .
And then I can 't ...
I can 't remember what happened after that .
- I guess we drank . - Yeah .
We drank and ... we drank .
Tom .
Tom ... what happened then ?
Then I ...
I must have fallen over ...
and woken up on ... on your couch .
The sun was in my eyes , I couldn 't see anything .
I didn 't know where I was .
You looked like you came out of the sun .
I could just see your silhouette .
And then when I ... I finally saw you ...
I realized where I was .
And then you spoke to me .
What did I say ?
You asked me if I wanted some scrambled eggs .
And ?
And that was that .
Yeah .
That was that .
I kinda felt like I was home ...
because of you .
I 'm ... I 'm home right now .
Tom ?
[ cries ]
[ sobs ]
[ footsteps approaching ]
[ continues sobbing ]
[ sobbing ]
[ cries ]
[ car door opens ]
- [ grunts ] - [ boy hisses ]
- [ screams ] - [ hissing continues ]
[ grunts ]
[ woman sobbing ]
[ boy clapping ]
[ Gemma grunts ]
[ grunts ]
[ wails ]
[ Gemma ] What am I ?
What is this ?
What am I in this ?
[ boy ] You are a mother .
- A mother ? - Yes .
Someone who prepares her son for the world .
[ Gemma ] What does a mother do then ?
[ boy ] She dies .
You go to sleep now .
Have a nice dream .
All we wanted ...
- was a home . - [ scoffs ] Silly Mother .
You are home .
[ muffled ] I 'm not your fucking mother .
Pardon ?
I said ...
I am not your fucking mother .
[ sighs ] Whatever .
♪ ♪
[ body thuds ]
[ door closes ]
[ gas tank closes ]
[ car engine starts ]
[ " 007 Shanty Town " by Desmond Dekker playing ]
♪ A shanty town ♪
♪ Dem rude boys get a probation ♪
♪ A shanty town ... ♪
♪ Soldier get longer ♪
♪ A shanty town ♪
♪ Rude boy a weep and a wail ♪
♪ A shanty town ... ♪
- [ Martin breathing heavily ] - [ shop bell rings ]
[ door closes ]
[ Martin grunts ]
[ exhales ]
[ air hissing ]
♪ ♪
[ body crunches ]
♪ I ask myself , should I put my finger to the left ? ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ I ask myself , should I put my finger to the right ? ♪
♪ Does it really matter where I put my finger ? ♪
♪ Someone else will come along and move it ♪
♪ And it 's always been the same ♪
♪ It 's just a complicated game ♪
♪ A little girl asked me ♪
♪ Should she part her hair upon the left ♪
♪ Uh-uh-uh-oh ♪
♪ A little girl asked me ♪
♪ Should she part her hair upon the right , no ♪
♪ I said It really doesn 't matter where you part your hair ♪
♪ For someone else will come along and move it ♪
♪ And it 's always been the same ♪
♪ It 's just a complicated game ♪
♪ A little boy asked me should he put his vote upon the left ♪
♪ A little boy asked me should he put his vote upon the right ♪
♪ I say it really doesn 't matter where you put your vote ♪
♪ ' Cause someone else will come along and move it ♪
♪ And it 's always been the same ♪
♪ It 's just a complicated game ♪
♪ Oh , it 's just a complicated game ♪
♪ They wanted Tom , they wanted Joe ♪
♪ To dress ' em up and stick ' em out on show ♪
♪ They were only arrows in a very bad aim ♪
♪ It 's just a complicated game ♪
[ instrumental break ]
♪ God asked me should he ought to put his world on the left ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ God asked me should he oughta put his world on the right , no ♪
♪ I said It doesn 't really matter where you put your world ♪
♪ Someone will come along and move it ♪
♪ And it 's always been the same ♪
♪ It 's just a complicated game ♪
♪ Just a complicated game ♪
♪ ♪
[ instrumental song playing ]